<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Glenn McComb: front end developer and designer</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Glenn McComb: front end developer and designer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 15:31:24 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Schecter C-7 Apocalypse</title><link>/articles/schecter-c7-apocalypse/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 15:31:24 +1100</pubDate><guid>/articles/schecter-c7-apocalypse/</guid><description>In early March of 2020 after months of searching and hunting, right before the Coronavirus lockdown kicked off in Australia, I bought my first ever 7-string - a Schecter C-7 Apocalypse.
It&amp;rsquo;s a great guitar, check out the photos! I also wrote about how I ended up with this guitar below the photos.  When I started my search I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking for a 7-string, but the more I researched, the more I began to think I&amp;rsquo;d like the extra range.</description></item><item><title>Smokey Gertrude</title><link>/photography/smokey-gertrude/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/photography/smokey-gertrude/</guid><description>Gertrude Street in Fitzroy in the days following the January 2020 bush fires in Australia.</description></item><item><title>Parliament Underground</title><link>/photography/parliament-underground/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/photography/parliament-underground/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Building a pure CSS animated SVG spinner</title><link>/articles/building-a-pure-css-animated-svg-spinner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 09:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/articles/building-a-pure-css-animated-svg-spinner/</guid><description>In this article I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to level up your loading indicators with a pure-CSS animated SVG loader inspired by Google&amp;rsquo;s Chrome and YouTube spinner.
What are we making? A good loading indicator helps users feel a sense of progress, and the spinner which Google uses for Chrome and YouTube is one of my favourites. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll be showing you how to make:</description></item><item><title>QV walkway</title><link>/photography/qv-walkway/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/photography/qv-walkway/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Creating smooth sequential animations with Sass</title><link>/articles/creating-smooth-sequential-animations-with-sass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 17:20:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/articles/creating-smooth-sequential-animations-with-sass/</guid><description>In this article I&amp;rsquo;m going to demonstrate a technique for creating CSS animations using the power of Sass&amp;rsquo; for loop. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re using React, Vue or Angular, these animations can be used in your app.
Why even animate things? Animations are a crucial ingredient in adding life and character to a website or application. They can make transitions feel faster even if they take more time than when they&amp;rsquo;re not animated.</description></item><item><title>Useful Sass (SCSS) media query mixins for Bootstrap</title><link>/articles/useful-sass-scss-media-query-mixins-for-bootstrap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 15:31:24 +1100</pubDate><guid>/articles/useful-sass-scss-media-query-mixins-for-bootstrap/</guid><description>Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to share some Sass (SCSS) mixins which I&amp;rsquo;ve found helpful when developing Bootstrap websites.
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re using full-blown Bootstrap or just leveraging the familiar grid they will save you time when writing repetitive media queries. Due to the similarities in naming conventions between Bootstrap 3 and 4, these mixins can be easily adapted for both versions.
They&amp;rsquo;re also versatile and work well even with your own custom naming conventions and breakpoints.</description></item><item><title>A better Rust menu interface</title><link>/articles/a-better-rust-menu-interface/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 20:28:46 +1100</pubDate><guid>/articles/a-better-rust-menu-interface/</guid><description>Rust&amp;rsquo;s menu interface is in need of an overhaul. The most heavily used screen — the server browser — functions the most poorly of all, so I&amp;rsquo;ve had a crack at improving it.
It&amp;rsquo;s difficult to find a server in Rust. When you find yourself using a 3rd party website (shouts to battlemetrics) to find a decent server something is clearly up.
Server browser redesign Here&amp;rsquo;s my attempt at improving the server browser:</description></item><item><title>Rust survival tips for newbies</title><link>/articles/rust-survival-tips-for-newbies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 01:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>/articles/rust-survival-tips-for-newbies/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve just started playing Rust or you&amp;rsquo;re looking for tips to help get a base down you&amp;rsquo;ve landed in the right place.
Rust is in early access and Facepunch are working to improve the experience for beginners before officially launching but unless you have friends who&amp;rsquo;re already playing, you&amp;rsquo;re on your own.
The first thing to know about Rust is that you will die. A lot. And that&amp;rsquo;s ok.</description></item><item><title>How to build custom Hugo pagination</title><link>/articles/how-to-build-custom-hugo-pagination/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 14:28:42 +1100</pubDate><guid>/articles/how-to-build-custom-hugo-pagination/</guid><description>Hugo is an awesome feature-packed static site generator which is also open source and free. It ships with a default pagination template but if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for full control, I&amp;rsquo;m going to demonstrate how to build custom pagination.
Introduction My focus in this tutorial is Hugo, so I won&amp;rsquo;t be writing CSS and I&amp;rsquo;ll use as little HTML as possible. I&amp;rsquo;ll be using some basic JavaScript examples to help explain Hugo&amp;rsquo;s syntax but JavaScript experience is unnecessary.</description></item><item><title>A better NBA box score</title><link>/articles/a-better-nba-box-score/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 09:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/articles/a-better-nba-box-score/</guid><description>After seeing a ton of respected NBA Twitter people — including LeBron James — complaining about poorly designed box scores, I endeavoured to improve the existing ESPN box score with a free Chrome extension.
It&amp;rsquo;s now my favourite way to follow an NBA game. Between this, Twitter and league pass I&amp;rsquo;m all set.
Layout Using custom CSS I updated the layout of the box score page so as the two teams sit side by side.</description></item><item><title>Royal Arcade</title><link>/photography/royal-arcade/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/photography/royal-arcade/</guid><description>Royal Arcade in Melbourne.</description></item><item><title>FitBugg</title><link>/work/fitbugg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 09:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/fitbugg/</guid><description>An iPhone app to help maintain your desired fitness level.</description></item><item><title>ESPN live score apps</title><link>/work/espn-live-score-apps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 04:02:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/work/espn-live-score-apps/</guid><description>A ground-up native re-design of ESPN Australia&amp;rsquo;s live score apps.</description></item></channel></rss>