<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development on Glenn McComb: front end developer and designer</title><link>/categories/development/</link><description>Recent content in Development on Glenn McComb: front end developer and designer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 09:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building a pure CSS animated SVG spinner</title><link>/articles/building-a-pure-css-animated-svg-spinner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 09:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/articles/building-a-pure-css-animated-svg-spinner/</guid><description>In this article I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to level up your loading indicators with a pure-CSS animated SVG loader inspired by Google&amp;rsquo;s Chrome and YouTube spinner.
What are we making? A good loading indicator helps users feel a sense of progress, and the spinner which Google uses for Chrome and YouTube is one of my favourites. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, here&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll be showing you how to make:</description></item><item><title>Creating smooth sequential animations with Sass</title><link>/articles/creating-smooth-sequential-animations-with-sass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 17:20:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/articles/creating-smooth-sequential-animations-with-sass/</guid><description>In this article I&amp;rsquo;m going to demonstrate a technique for creating CSS animations using the power of Sass&amp;rsquo; for loop. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re using React, Vue or Angular, these animations can be used in your app.
Why even animate things? Animations are a crucial ingredient in adding life and character to a website or application. They can make transitions feel faster even if they take more time than when they&amp;rsquo;re not animated.</description></item><item><title>A better NBA box score</title><link>/articles/a-better-nba-box-score/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 09:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>/articles/a-better-nba-box-score/</guid><description>After seeing a ton of respected NBA Twitter people — including LeBron James — complaining about poorly designed box scores, I endeavoured to improve the existing ESPN box score with a free Chrome extension.
It&amp;rsquo;s now my favourite way to follow an NBA game. Between this, Twitter and league pass I&amp;rsquo;m all set.
Layout Using custom CSS I updated the layout of the box score page so as the two teams sit side by side.</description></item></channel></rss>